let questions = [{
  question: "What is the baby of the Moth know as?",
  choices:['baby', 'infant', 'kit', 'larva'],
  correctAnswer: 3
},
{
  question:"What is the adult of a kid called",
  choices:['calf', 'doe', 'goat', 'chick'],
  correctAnswer: 2
},
{
  question:"What is the young of a bufallo called?",
  choices:['calf', 'baby', 'pup', 'cow'],
  correctAnswer: 0
},
{
  question:"What a baby alligator called?",
  choices:['baby', 'gator', 'hatchling', 'calf'],
  correctAnswer: 2
},
{
  question:"What is the baby Goose called?",
  choices:['gooser', 'gosling', 'gup', 'pup'],
  correctAnswer: 1
},
{
  question:"What is the baby Hamster called",
  choices:['pup', 'chick', 'infant', 'billy'],
  correctAnswer: 0
},
{
  question:"What is a baby Hawk called",
  choices:['hawklett', 'pup', 'larva', 'eyeas'],
  correctAnswer: 3
},
{
  question:"What is a baby gasshopper called",
  choices:['hopper', 'nymph', 'stick', 'pup'],
  correctAnswer: 1
},
{
  question:"What is a baby Kangaroo called",
  choices:['kinga', 'joey', 'calf', 'baby'],
  correctAnswer: 1
},
{
  question:"What is a baby Whale called",
  choices:['whala', 'cub', 'grub', 'infant'],
  correctAnswer: 1
},
{
  question:"What is a baby Monkey called",
  choices:['infant', 'baby', 'calf', 'pup'],
  correctAnswer: 0
},
{
  question:"What is a baby Bear called",
  choices:['cub', 'baby balu', 'young bear', 'bearlet'],
  correctAnswer: 2
}];